I wanna see you dancing to this one! Chicago!
The city's quiet, the sun is down. We're in the
glory of the side of town. The beat is calling
from a place I know. Just follow the sound and let
it go. We're dancing in the neon. Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh. We're moving till the night is gone. Oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh. Forget about tomorrow. We're
shining like a light. Dancing in the neon
tonight Dancing in the neon tonight
The sun's heavy, up, flashing by Reflected
colors in your eyes I don't care what the real
world wants This moment's all that I could ever
want We're dancing in the neon Oh, oh, oh, oh
We're moving till the night is gone Oh, oh, oh, oh
Forget about tomorrow We're shining like a
light Dancing in the neon tonight
Don't stop, don't stop the feeling This music's
got me feeling Don't stop, don't stop the beat
Dancing in the neon tonight
We're dancing in the neon.
We're moving to the night.
Forget about tomorrow. We're shining like a
light. Dancing in the neon tonight.
Dancing in the neon tonight. Dancing.
In the night
So the night is gone